https://www.nch.com.au/general/privacy.html

Introduction
We at NCH Software are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. NCH Software has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information.
For the purposes of this statement, "Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit NCH Software's Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.
If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the Web, we reserve the right to transfer that Information within NCH Software or to NCH Software's third-party service providers, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world.
NCH Software strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, NCH Software intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an "adequate" level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.
Back to top
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about website activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.
We use cookies to track users on our website in order to improve our website presence. For example, we use the information to assist us in deciding how to order links. We also use cookies to track from where visitors to our site find us. We never store personal information in cookies. We will never provide cookie information to third parties.
Back to top
Collection of Email Addresses
We will never sell your email address.
If you opt-in for our version update newsletter or purchase software from us we may send you marketing material. You will be able to unsubscribe at any time.
Your email address may be recorded by the software automatically, even if you do not opt-in. In this case we will not send you marketing material (unless you later chose to opt-in on purchase). Use of your email address will be limited to extreme cases such as notifying users of serious bugs in an application or no more than once for non-marketing product feedback requests.
Back to top
Collection of Program Usage Data
Our programs may collect anonymous usage data which may be sent back to use for analysis, such as the number of times a menu or option is used within the program. In these cases the data collected will never contain anything that can personally identify you.
Back to top
Choice
You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to NCH Software. Please review the Personal Information section of the Introduction in order to make this decision. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of NCH Software's Web sites, but you may be unable to download or purchase our software. If you chose to have a relationship with us, such as a contractual or other business relationship or partnership, we will naturally continue to contact you in connection with that business relationship.
Back to top
Popular Software
Audio Editing Software
Disc Burner
Avi Converter
Mp3 Converter
Sound File Converter
Audio Recording Software
Security
Wherever your Personal Information may be held within NCH Software, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Our site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and unauthorized alteration of the information under our control. More specifically, our server uses SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) security protection by encrypting all of your personal information including credit card number, name and address to prevent individuals from reading this information as it travels over the Internet.
Back to top
Access/Accuracy
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, NCH Software wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting NCH Software should you need to update or correct that Information.
Back to top
Third Party Services
NCH Software does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on NCH Software's behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against NCH Software's policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.
Some NCH Software applications make use of Google API Services for features such as file or video sharing. If you authorize an application to use your Google Account, the application will store an access token on your device. To invalidate this token at any time, follow the Remove site or app access instructions at Google Account Help.
Back to top
Children's Privacy
NCH Software's website is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.
Back to top
Commitment
Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and NCH Software's Web site is constantly evolving to meet these demands.
If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please Contact Us. While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.
Back to top
Your Consent
By using this website, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to NCH Software's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explaining NCH Software's policies pertaining to collection of Personal Information on the Web. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.
Back to top
Changes to this Privacy Policy
NCH Software reserves the right to occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback or changes to privacy legislation. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how NCH Software is protecting your personal information.
Back to top
Related Links
Home
Testimonials
Software Awards
Most Popular Software
Music Editing Software
CD Burner
